all right hello and welcome it is August
5th
2024 this is active infer ant stream dou
1.1 new stream series just dropped and
this is where we're headed today we're
going to be doing linguistic analysis on
fully synthetic all by all dissertations
we're going to go into a lot more detail
on what that means but just quickly at
the top level each of these points in a
principal component semantic space is a
written
dissertation shifting from one field to
another following on on the lab of Mike
Lev at all who who worked on the field
shift one this is field shift 2 it does
quite a few different things and for
example this data point is the actual
term frequency usage Distribution on
synthetic negotiation to synthetic
Quantum computation I'll talk more about
what the synthetic part means this is
like a PhD dissertation that's going
from negotiation to Quantum computation
and here we have similarity clustering
across in all by all of different
domains so we're going to be going to a
lot of different places and ways let's
just start with this text file off the
bat super excited for this it's been
really rapidly developing I'm using
cursor 0.39 came out just a few days ago
even better than the prior ones so let's
start this off right I'm going to push
3,000
files to a major get
release this is going to take a few
minutes once it
pushes push that now all right once that
pushes
then I'm going
to come over to zenodo and make a new
release on GitHub so first just wanted
while that's loading you see it on the
top of the
page so noo makes it super easy to
connect GitHub
repos via zenodo who offers dois digital
object identifiers so active inference
is right here once the GitHub push is
completed then we'll make a release of
the
repo and then that will get a new dii
and archive it on Zoda
so that's really awesome so just a few
different tools using zodo for
publishing for Di GitHub for code and
let's reload it see if we're
in one minute ago active infant
stream1 so now
let's make a new
release this is going to
be number 0 1.1
needs a tag
1.01 during the
stream publish
it 1.1 is
published reload on
zenodo and it'll probably take a few
minutes but that's pretty cool because
then it'll also have the
DOI coming from zenodo and the archiving
so maybe we'll check back there
later okay let us go
to these are it's in the background it's
translating the dissertations into
Sanskrit and Arabic in the background so
hence these new files being added but
we're going to get all there okay start
with GitHub push done reload and confirm
update make the GitHub update we did
that and we're using cursor 0.39 came
out a few days ago okay for backup
there's a
page in the active block for inst
Cota
so it summarizes a little bit about
field shift so I'm doing this that's
right now August 5th 16 UTC the codes in
active infrance just uploaded now
what field shift 2 is doing right now is
generating thousands of these all by all
domain a to domain B and I borrow this
term and develop in the same tradition
from Mike Lan at all's work so here's
the paper here machine learning for
hypothesis generation in biology and
Medicine exploring the latent space of
Neuroscience and developmental
bioelectricity O'Brien at all 11 so they
uh briefly
let's see if the figure is a little bit
bigger they briefly describe how AI is
playing an important and pervasive role
in the scientific
process they talk about analogies and
isomorphisms between for example the
neural synopse and the cellular Junction
bio electrically and chemically
considered they talk about some even
broader quote functional invariance
between neuros science and developmental
biology so that sounds kind of cool
promising of course
metaphor here's the BART based domain
translator this relates to taking
material from One content and then
putting it into an encoder gets
decoded and here they provide the
outline of a gp4 based domain translator
so Neuroscience Concepts and
developmental biology concepts are
juxtapose I'll show what their data
looked like in a second
and they used that they also had
annotators they had several person
annotators and they tested how how well
were the ideas that it came up with they
just showed that a few of the kinds of
cases that they tested and then did some
preliminary go type analyses looking at
like were these hypotheses better than a
uniform random distribution so that was
really inspiring and I had shared
previously with Mike Lev the sort of
Mike lev. py from elsewhere in the
research methods folder um so I thought
that that was pretty cool let's look at
field shift one and then we're going to
go through field shift 2 so what field
shift one is first I brought the whole
paper's plain text in because then I can
use this and say what what would field
shift one think about this and then
here's what their data sets look like so
they had one expression so many memories
come to mind so many pattern memories
come to the body so they have
a kind
of expression from the Neuroscience
domain and then an expression that's
analogous deemed to be analogous from
the developmental biology frame so I
started playing with that and playing
with that and playing with that so
here's where we we got to I'll start
with what are called domains so this is
in field shift 2 now
domains I have here ATM transactions
biology blockchain Buckminster Fuller
chemistry cognitive security cooking
entomology fabric free energy principle
active inference healthc care
Hospitality hopa that's the ants the
bees and the Wasps the soft flies
Logistics mitochondrial biology
negotiation Neuroscience prediction
matter expertise Quantum computation
spatial web traditional wisdom William
Blake uh and we can make another
synthetic domain so if anybody is in the
chat and they want to request a domain I
will um see if we can make it on the Fly
I'll show what it looks like but while
somebody is posting a fun domain to add
it can be as narrow it could be entering
the third digit of the pin in the ATM
transaction or it could be like that
corner but not this corner because a
domain it's it could be an ism it could
be a kind of a person it can be an
entity so it's it significantly
generalizes on what I had above with the
entities but here's what the structure
of these files are so the first line
with a hashtag is saying what the domain
is just its name
then there are several dozens to several
hundred examples and
questions also depending on the
situation and how it was generated and
all this other things here like a fact
so chemistry may have definitions
examples all right Vladimir wrote
intelligent soft matter excellent I will
add this so new file
synthetic intelligent soft m matter.
MD okay # intelligence soft
matter control
okay
so contrl a contrl k inline editing
using Cloud 3.5
Sonet we're in the domain folder
new file that was just
created in the syntactic
style of at
cooking so synthetic these are I just
want to pick a few of the
synthetics at
markdown uh markdown transaction at Hop
uh synthetic chemistry let's just see if
one is enough please write many relevant
professional concise
statements and
questions related to intelligent soft
matter so that's why I describe these
knowledge bases as synthetic because
they're being entirely
synthesized in the file I'm not bringing
in any transcripts or any factual
databases I'm just saying generate
likely
expressions giving the the topic so
it'll take a while I've I've way way
rate limited the um cursor so here we
go
definitions example definition example
fact intelligent soft matter often
incorporates nanom materials to enhance
functionality and
responsiveness okay so looks good crl A
contrl K please so now it knows exactly
the format too please add many relevant
examples and
questions but the semantics of what are
broadly there are already defined so
let's just let it do one more pass then
this is perfect because it'll um it'll
expand our domains from
22 to 23 okay I'll I'll add one more for
um Michael lenon then with the 24 we'll
push the 24 through the whole uh outline
here's here here's the visualization
here's what's going to
happen first we're going to generate the
input domains that's where we're going
to have 24 of them in this case then
we're going to generate Pro shifted
domains these are just going to be like
concatenated text files that will get
sent off to the
llm it it doesn't have to be its own
script or anything like that but what
the shift domains. py does is it's going
to send this concatenated list of all by
all domain shifts so basic basically
prompt then domain a then domain B shift
domains is going to send that to open
API open AI API get back a shifted
domain the shifted domain is going to
get prompted again to the llm and it
will say make a dissertation outline
with this structure so then there's a
dissertation outline for each all by all
then from the outline generate it then
this is another llm step then from the
draft improve it LOL
draft then translate it into a variety
of languages and just on the language
side this is what that will look
like translated dissertations here's the
folders Spanish Sanskrit Russian Punjabi
Portuguese Navajo it's really
interesting what it says for different
languages what it will and won't
do and then at any of these steps we're
basically just talking about a folder of
markdown files so we can use a variety
of language uh meta analytic methods and
use those kinds of landscapes for for
our own
use
okay back to soft matter okay I just
wrote please add many relevant examples
and
questions so these can be you can add in
more factual information or specific
information so now we're up
to we
go field shift two just refresh the
folder inputs and outputs domain
okay let's add the the one
that Michael Lennon said just do this
and then we'll push both of those on
through the all by
all non-science ways of
knowing in the in the syntactic style of
at
intelligent soft matter the one we just
generated same
request here's intelligence of matter in
the file structure
yeah and this is like gets fascinating
with well what does the llm SL pipeline
think are likely Salient acceptable safe
responses to asking about this or
that thank you for the gift up cycle
club who wrote stigar G ant
Emoji all
right 7 2
statements interesting citizen science
initiatives we'll just do one more
expansion add many more
relevant examples and
questions all right then we're going to
with those 24 domains then we're going
to push through the all by all but
previously we had 22 domains and so that
generated 444 484 pro- shifted domains
so let's look at these fil
this is just a concatenated
file so here's the prompt it's going to
say
whoa The Prompt is you're an expert
follow these steps for the domain
transposition there's 12 steps and
here's the output okay here's domain go
here's the synthetic statements on ATM
trans
actions all of
them then at a roughly equal length here
now where domain B is chemistry so then
this is going to be
ATM isomorphy transposed onto chemistry
so it's like the way that people might
think about things and the reverse so
gripper and gripped push and pull
swapping perspective swapping there and
back back back and out all right now we
have 24 um okay so kind of come along in
the cursor and in the file structure so
first
thing in the terminal just clear LS in
the directory with the scripts so we go
to the visualization first we had the
input domains generate Pro ship
domains okay total domains processed
24 to the output
directory re okay now we're at 576 Pro
shifted
domains
okay now we're ready to do the domain
shift shift underscore
domains okay it skips files that Ed had
already
output so while it's doing that first
domain
shift
awesome while it's doing that first
domain shift and it'll report the timing
which one it did Dean asked in the chat
can you explain field shift in a scale
friendly as compared to a scale-free
perspective let's revisit that but it's
a great question it makes me think of
tilt shift
photography depth of
field so here's what happened the ones
that we already had the 484 of the
576 those were skipped so then we got to
the First new field shift and we'll
we'll look at the script also but it's
nothing more than the text file Plus
open
AI synthetic Neuroscience so
Neuroscience Concepts transposed onto
intelligent soft matter next new one was
so that took 22 seconds they're taking
up 19 to 23
seconds now in the inputs outputs reload
it so pro- shifted domains is 576 that's
our cap but in the shifted domain SD
file we're at 47 because we finished
three so that is going to keep um
plugging
meanwhile it was just translating in the
background to have
more now just we can already start to
push we'll run it again later to catch
up but we can already take the next step
with the
488 shifted domains okay so pull back to
the
visualization what does the shifted
domain look like and then how how are we
going to use that to write the
dissertation
outline so here let's look
at Logistics applied to
hop so every single all by all was just
the concatenation of you're a prompt
expert you're about to do this domain
shift here's domain a here's domain B
make the shift so here's what the shift
domain
yields so deep analysis of domain a and
this could be structured with systems
thinking Lon colie George Mobis etc etc
etc it would be awesome and there's many
more structured that's been one of the
most surprising learnings overall of the
last like uh five days is yeah there's
some structured ways to do cognitive
modeling claims analysis rhetorical
analysis all these kinds of Concepts
however especially with cursor in the
game
there's so much that can already be
brought forth with this rough or fuzzy
probabilistic blob and hope strategy so
domain a deep
analysis domain B separate
analysis identification of isomorphy
isomorphy sorry identif identify
isomorphism so similarities and
structure between A and
B transposition of fundamental elements
novel hypothesis and theory ant colony
Supply Chain management develop a new
lexicon who's on first outline a
research agenda Envision Revolution
revolutionizing education identify
technological innovations anticipate
resistance limitations propose inter
disciplinary collaborations construct a
compelling narrative so those were the
12 sections from The Prompt so that's
why these shifted responses are just
responding to the structure that was
suggested by prompt so now we're going
to go from those shifted domains which
are just kind of like fact sheet type
reports now we're going to go from the
shifted domain to the dissertation
outline
generator dissertation tab outline
generator similar where the dissertation
output file already exists it skips it
now it's going to be writing an outline
so now let's go to what let's look at
the dissertation outline
script all right so first generate Pro
shift domains just really
fast
logging cursor incredible for helping
logging and and bugging and debugging
here's the concatenation prompt domain a
domain
B please prepare yourself to make a
shift domain here's domain a here's
domain B for all domains that outputs
that concatenation okay now we go to the
out the outline
generator Dean asks are those AB
isomorphisms assumed stable it's a great
question put it this way if you didn't
change a text file and you ran the same
computer it would give probabilistic
ically within that envelope the same
quote
results which may or may not reflect how
things actually were of course you can
make synthetic domain you can make
custom domains you could do Harry Potter
you could make different um domains that
that also don't have anything to do with
anything so maybe you could say this is
this is the platonic solid domain this
is just very few Expressions very
accurate all right outline generator
again logging getting the open AI API
key this is kept in in like two ways in
the M environment file and llm keys. key
both of them are in the git
ignore so you can put private and I
won't open them on the stream but then
it enables the scripts to use the API so
you can just change that one file like
figure out what your API key is put it
into one of these kinds of files and
then basically there's a way to do it so
generate the dissertation
outline this one I used another method
relatively so instead of whereas in the
um
um in this
concatenator I set the prompt as a
variable and then just concatenated
three variables so there could be
different prompts put in there like it
could go a lot of different other ways
just to at the at the outset because the
prompt here is going to sort of direct
how everything it's it's more Upstream
whereas in the dissertation outline
generator now here's the structure of
the dissertation
by adding many sections even if it only
gives like one to three sentences in
each of the sections it's still going to
have a good length so it just says
provide um you're creating a
comprehensive groundbreaking PhD
dissertation plan for newly shifted
domain this
domain represents a fusion
Etc it does these could be on new lines
it doesn't really matter your task is to
create a detailed expansive
intellectually rigorous dissertation
plan that articulates
Etc long
line using the provided shifted domain
description so that's that kind of like
fact sheet report like here's how
Logistics could apply to himon optra
develop a massive dissertation
play then here's the structure
expected that's
it
then it concatenates it with the so that
fixed prompt plus the
um shifted
domain that
yields shifted domain dissertation
outline so now this is starting to get
bumped up from 484 to 493 so let's look
at one of these new shifted
domains outlines so let's look at
see if any have been written for the
matter
yet let's see which ones have just been
written most
recently okay synthetic Hospitality to
synthetic intelligence soft
matter so you it this could be a
Hospitality lab saying let's go into
soft matter could be the soft matter lab
saying let's go into Hospitality but
look at this one and the other
flip
okay
so personalization service quality and
sustainability from Hospitality the
research aims to redefine the
capabilities of soft materials creating
responsive user Centric designs that
adapt to environmental stimuli so
background um on the shifted domain
novelty
overarching
questions so again this is the direction
of going how can the principles of guest
experience be applied to the design and
functionality of intelligent soft
materials whereas the text file that
says intelligent soft matter to
hospitality will say what can we learn
from intelligent soft matter that will
help us in the hospitality questions and
situations then it has all the
structures okay new theoretical
constructs emerging from the ship
so this one these are actually sometimes
super funny um and and there could be
sections like add more puns and memes
and everything but responsive experience
Theory user interactions with materials
can enhance functionality and
satisfaction H like the
material it's it's not like its
properties are just a priori and fixed
they're interactive so there's a a
relationship with the responsibity
materials quality assurance Model A
framework for assessing intelligent
materials based based on user experience
metrics again let let in the All by all
seman uh landscape let let that be the
starting point but if there's a if it's
a variant or if it's like another way to
go then that's just the starting point
so that just gets the conversation going
um methods
ethical personalized soft matter quality
metrics for materials smart integration
sustainable design principle
interdisiplinary implications practical
applications future research
conclusion let's look
at another recent
one okay entomology to nonscience ways
of knowing dissertation plan
how can the principles of Entomology
inform personal development Community
resilience what new theoretical
constructs emerge from the intersection
of Entomology and non-science ways of
knowing in what ways can this shifted
domain influence educational practices
societal
structures metamorphosis as
transformation social structures in
community communication models
ecological wisdom
Etc thank you Michael and Dean great
comments All
right so back to the
visualization so that was generating the
dissertation
outline next dissertation generator.
py same
logic skipping the files that already
existed let's look at what the
dissertation looks like
so shifted dissertations 484 that was
the starting
number so these were the ones that were
there
earlier how about cooking
to free energy principle active
inference
by analyzing how flavor profiles cooking
techniques and culinary Fusion can be
understood through predictive coding and
variational free energy this research
chics to redefine culinary arts and
enhance the dining
experience how can culinary practices be
modeled as adaptive systems that
minimize free
energy what role do predictive coding
and variational free energy play in the
development of flavor profiles and
cooking techniques in what ways can this
interdisciplinary approach influence
culinary education Etc
new theoretical constructs culinary
systems as adaptive
systems the role of sensory
feedback
okay here 36 seconds it also includes
the self it didn't exclude the the a
shift to a so that's actually another
informative Loop about about what's
there all right but now we have some new
ones
refresh
okay Neuroscience to non-science ways of
knowing
the significance of This research lies
in its intive approach to knowledge
integration challenging traditional
boundaries between science and
non-science by leveraging insights from
Neuroscience etc etc
etc how can principles from Neuroscience
be applied to understand and enhance
cultural practices
how what are the implications of
cultural neuroplasticity for Community
resilience and adaptation how do
cultural narratives function as symbolic
Messengers that influence emotional
states and behavior havior what
interdisciplinary methodologies can be
developed to facilitate this integration
of knowledge history ronal non-science
ways of
knowing new theoretical constructs
cultural neuroplasticity
Theory maybe it's drawn from somewhere
maybe it's just a
synthesis symbolic transmission
hypothesis whatever is in the schema for
the dissertation it will write something
with that output there's a few
situations where where especially in
Translation and things we'll say oh I
don't really do
that
okay let's let's just carry carry on um
in the
pipeline then that that's the
dissertation
draft so this should maybe be
dissertation draft generator but
obviously it's all a draft
so the dissertation
improver okay
so it's
it you can open a new terminal window if
you want to have another open um edge
with the
API but
um let's
um just terminate the one
that's Shifting the domains so that's
how many we'll we'll just carry forth
okay all right dissertation improver
skips the ones that are already written
it's going to now it's hitting new ones
that are also getting pumped in from
here this could be coordinated like a
lot uh better all right dissertation
improver okay this could be iterative
there could be different rounds of of
commentary so that was again one of the
most shocking SL interesting things was
um uh on on two two different domains so
at the structure at the level of
sections of a document like structuring
modular publishing and all these kinds
of efforts and at the level of
structuring like agents and reviewers
and critiquer and actor Network model so
here's where both of those I was
surprised
on for the document
composition there's very good adherence
to this to the prompts
like I'm using here like every single
PhD outline uses the exact one that's
requested so you could add more sections
and add the token length and everything
um add different sections you could
request a different kind of document
structured with certain subsections that
like do or don't make sense with
relationship to your your input
folder um so yes it's very strong and
interesting to pursue
the strongly composable document
composition
however
using clear prompts is giving documents
with good structure then on this level
of like multi-agent science science
agents um writing massive writing all
these kinds of things um there's a lot
of like flow like what if this went to
here and that went to here and I think
again that's very interesting and yakob
smol and I wrote the generative research
teams the grts that discusses a lot and
it was exciting okay had to active
inference agents and other kinds of of
intelligences work together ecosystem of
shared intelligence um AOS the the
active entity onology for science back
in the DSi 2022 days all those kinds of
directions like let's have some kind of
interoperable strong message passing and
again I think that is going to be a
strong and a vital element but here with
the total cost of millions of tokens
still under the tens of
cense at least using cursor it it's been
easier to just do all by all all by all
all by
all and just filter folders of markdown
files but then just do another
combinatory explosion and then filter
down and also there's an interesting
connection there with how that kind of
relates to um abductive inference and
the two-stroke Engine with generating
and then winwing so so that's actually
super interesting too because it turns
out I'm not saying well if we connected
this one to Blake and that in fabric
science it's like just blast filter if
needed but if it's not even need it's
just text files and it's only a few
hundreds to hundreds of thousands should
be fine so dissertation
improver you're a worldclass academic
writer task with improving an existing
PhD
dissertation enhance it in these 10 ways
follow these guidelines like only add
things make it better make table added
hypotheses enhance the language you
could you know whatever it happens to be
here's the dissertation to
improve insert dissertation in the
concatenated file please do it
now so here's improving dissertation
chemistry to soft matter so some of
these it's like and again this is what
the language analyses show um like in
the semantic spaces in their own
different ways whether at the syntactic
or the semantic excit is like okay
chemistry to chemistry or chemistry to
Quantum or chemistry to soft matter
those might like cluster closer that's
the exact kind of thing that we do
measure and analyze and this is just a
representative image here because you
could imagine all kinds of linguistic um
analyses there so let's go to the
improved
dissertations this slightly um um
increases their length I didn't analyze
the distribution but like they're all
kind of like over 20
mostly so shifted dissertations that was
the input improved
once Let's
do let's just look at one that was
already oh well blockchain to Logistics
everyone knows about that one it's like
okay how about ATM transaction to Bucky
Fuller by transposing the efficiency
accessibility and security of ATM
transactions into Fuller's framework of
sustainable Design Systems thinking this
research aims to develop a novel model
for resource management and Service
delivery the proposed daxian kiosk it's
like new post Fuller term just dropped
will serve as a practical application of
this
model addressing Global challenges
through Community engagement in in
technology okay Dean
says Michael says it's hilarious and yet
strangely educational
absolutely and and I think another
thread to pull on it's like this is
simpler it's so different you know
catastrophically different than 2014 to
2019 doing my PhD with limited computer
field workor less video chatting but it
it's it's easier to just handle the
folder slash different so it's it's just
it's all you know different is different
and then Dean says can you build in
information mutation at some specific
level would that help the wh ifs over
the derivative intersection yeah yeah
that's like someone just says like this
is just like pulling a crank like like
you
um you're just like moving strings of
pasta forward and then they're just
going to be all headed for the trash
pile but what you could do is you could
be like okay like Okay cooking to
Logistics that's kind of interesting
maybe there's a grant program or there's
like a PhD student applicant volunteer
who thinks this is like funny and then
synthetic cooking Logistics but it's
just a text file so now later we're
going to translate this but you could
change this and just say we're redacting
this part you know replacing that one
with that part
I'm not going to save it but you can
change this or you could write another
script that says mutate and it just does
any kind of mutation to any subset of
these text files okay so then back to
the
visualization now it's
translated
dissertation
translation again it's so cheap per
translation below below sense per
operation so here's
translation here's the list of
languages we're going to look into the
folder and just see what it outputs for
some of
these translated dissertations so by
language folder
okay
here's Neuroscience to William Blake in
Bengali can't read it
chemistry onto itself in
Hindi
okay languages with uh data sets that
are
large have strong complete
translations we can tell just by looking
at the file sizes here so for Hindi
they're all 34 is here we have a a range
which is interesting so here's a smaller
one here's very
small I cannot provide a translation of
an entire PhD dissertation into
Navajo here's a longer
one translating a PhD dissertation into
Navajo while maintaining High academic
quality and Technical accuracy is a
complex task that requires deep
understanding of both languages and the
subject matter
below is a translation of the provided
dissertation into Navajo following the
guidelines you
specified neuro Neuroscience onto
cognitive
security so here it's like I won't but
then I did 14 here's a
4.3 okay it's going to be hard it's a
complex task
however I can provide a sample
translation of a portion of the
dissertation to demonstrate how this can
be
approached please note that due to the
limitations of this platform which one I
will provide a translation of the
executive summary and introduction
sections only
okay
so then that's a glimpse into how it
could be
translated so look just in the file size
you can see heterogeneity and and
uh uh both
sism when there's
little
information
similarly Sami there's a 228
version let's read it I can't do
it and then an even smaller
version I can't do
it but the ones with a lot of training
data they have large consistent file
sizes so here it is also logging taking
one minute less than a cent per
translation skip the ones that it had
done 72 67 58 all
right uh language analysis last thing
then we'll just do some other random uh
improvements
and look at Super chats and
everything Michael Lennon says I feel
like I'm witnessing a shifting a pushing
of the boundaries of what does science
knowledge work in the near future thank
you Michael thank you I'm super happy to
be able to share this
uh
and for it to be open source and for
there to be so many affordances for
people to contribute
and fork and
clone all right language
analysis let's well let's just see what
we have running right now okay so this
now this one is um finished so you you
right now the orchestration like you you
kind of have to comb over the folder a
few times or you could do let it all
shift then let it all write the outline
Etc or you could add multiple um
multi-thread Computing but these kinds
of things are what cursor at all are
incredible on it's like selecting a
piece of code and then just saying
contrl K or control shift L saying make
this run on N
processors and then there are ways that
it will do it
well okay so from the terminal again
clear
okay synthetic domains or it could have
been real data or any kind of data all
these are just text file outputs you can
mutate them arbitrarily at every single
step no need for agent orchestration
just good old bioinformatic style text
file input domains but not saying that
that there wouldn't be cases where you'd
have higher efficiency Etc with more
nuanced approaches and different things
input domains they were fully synthetic
in this case we had start 22 then we
bumped it to 24
with Vladimir and Michael's suggestion
concatenate prep optional step if you
want you can just batch these two shift
domains makes the situation report on
the
shift write the dissertation outline
according to how you say it
is generate the draft from the
outline improve it once expand it add
unique hypotheses Etc now translate to n
languages in their own folder and then
last script for now just the language
analysis
um oh now it's
called metaanalysis shifted
dissertation all right so it's running
in the terminal processing text so this
is a local computation this is not using
the AI um or open API Etc
um you define the input and the output
folder so here we're going to be looking
at the analysis for the first
dissertation draft but you just change
the input folder and you can make it
look at any folder
um the these are just examples of
linguistic analyses
again I just control a and just like add
more relevant interesting visual
outputs to each
folder or make a new kind of folder or
make me something that will reflect my
curiosity about X okay so the script on
the prior version slash on disk quote
disk is here running but now we're also
live editing we're we're confirming that
the prior version
works there kind of like a little Nano
git because then if I accept these green
edits and just rerun it right
away either it'll continue to run or
it'll not okay so here's can now it's
added networks interactive and
dendrograms will they work let's find
out scanning over the parts that are
already that are just not being touched
but there's times where it will just say
oh deletes a huge block of code or
there's times where it just does things
that that move you in
circles but you get to see a lot of code
and it's a a well structured code to in
at least to this nonprofessional
programmers uh cursor enhanced
way so it's it's a simpler semantic
layer whereas programming when it got
lost in the in the obscurity of where
the bracket is closing it gets really
down
there okay so I'm just going to close
that prior version clear save the script
so if if this works then we'll see new
things popping up in this analyses
dissertations so if if that that will
pop up in these new folders but let then
here's here's what these folders have
now
so this is principal component
analysis K means
clustering Matrix decomposition methods
tne not saying these are the most like
performance or anything so many visual
improvements but just to say those are
clustering methods
um oh this one will the the the axes may
need to be adjusted depending on how
many um
like terms are in there okay top
terms okay top 30 Terms across all
documents okay
okay this is just the PCA kind of L that
we saw before but there's a shading like
a 95% density so this could be used like
okay what's that one that one that one
and that one or like you know and and
then then there's the PCA
interpretability methods which look like
so here's
here's okay so here's pc1 and PC2 these
are the these are linear decompositions
and and variance quote
explanation so here PCA component one so
this explains the greatest linear
fraction of the variance just to kind of
pull back one more step on the
pca's every time you take a
PC you're explaining more variants
that's what what it's called it's not in
the causal sense it's the correlational
kind of explanation here um but you're
always going to explain more variants
because you can always get some but then
you look at the accumulation curve of
the explained variance okay maybe you
know and then you could either calculate
like oh this is the optimum or we only
have space for three but it's good to
know that it's only
18% um okay so here's one and two each
data point is a written outline so
written file names can be improved ET
so
negotiation is highly weighted on this
and Quantum is negative so documents
that use negotiation
negotiators conflict strategies
resolution these are to the right on pc1
documents that mention Quantum or to
left PC2 which is the y- AIS
is um associated with the use of the
word
Quantum and for example not the word
culinary or
mitochondrial let like okay yeah Quantum
is up and to the right Etc
so that's kind of what these plots are
showing but then Landscapes and so oh
what would be right here what would be
like that
one okay term loadings let's see if it
works okay specific terms here's again
Quantum is is low on pc1 high on
PC2 negotiation is slightly high on PC2
very far outlier you might get more
resolution like on this analysis by by
just excluding these three terms but
this is just one way to do the
analysis okay it's still chugging along
but yeah you can extract what are the
terms that are in each principal
component so that's the kind of semantic
space okay let's see while the
visualization method um is running
so so like here the translations are
just chugging along
chemistry to cooking in
Portuguese chemistry to cooking Bengali
now it's just looping through these
languages
okay all right so to return to this kind
of overall
one but we'll watch the visual script
Run Okay End to End All by all field
shifting
domains can
be synthetic or
Etc dissertation outlining expansion
into a draft draft Improvement draft
translation meta analytic methods these
are shown in the
visualization but the visualization was
just like CR a contrl k make aski art
for
this I think combining it with the grant
methods that that are in another uh
Corner uh of this
repo
here that's one
adjacency upcoming developments okay
incorporation of the entity and
organization cognitive model so just
again this was on the sort of how
structured does a cognitive model need
to be it was like here's fields. py
Chris
Fields now these are not even real
quotes necessarily but they were drawn
from these six I I draw the six
interviews in here's friston Bucky
Fuller Deborah Gordon Etc and yes
there's other people thrown in so it's
it's it's nowhere
near
um anything like a structured cognitive
model let alone like the kinds of re
real speaker sorted transcripts that
that many people in organizations have
this was just taking a few podcasts with
these people and then just distilling it
and this this we can go into it like
another time where we can add an entity
if somebody wants uh they're again
they're these condensed quotes but
depending on how you prompt it okay
giving a vision plotting here but let's
see if it output anything else these are
these like py pseudo code is quy now
they could be interoperable if you had a
schema defined maybe PhD student could
work on that um but then they can also
be
loose but bringing the entity and saying
okay how could these two entities like
this organization and and this person or
these two people or these two
organizations these three concatenate
their entity models like we can even do
this and then say how could they refract
through this shifted PhD dissertation to
that
Grant what if you can compose it it's at
least
plausible
okay entity and organization cognitive
models integration of Grant
uh proposals per research meod secure
funding for PhD projects and just sort
of you know
more uh explain like I am dot dot dot so
we we could concatenate a prompt that's
like um
explain this
shifted um about the dissertation that's
applying ATM transactions to cognitive
security
explain that like it's this kind of
event to this
person it it never is
gonna at least be interesting and funny
what it shows
okay
okay thank you Michael for your great
comments always very
insightful okay so then we we could do
how would you explain this to dot dot
dot and then that generalizes oh 17 18
19 20 but then so what does the model
think about how you should explain
something and then it's like well let's
call multiple
models if they're getting so so so
available now that's the whole deeper
questions about like externalities Etc
Grant methods okay just as a brief uh
recap well I'll put the uh in the live
chat here's
the field shift
Koda here's the gram
method so this is this was from prior uh
so this kind of goes through what the
grant concatenation methods do I'm not
going to go through it on this stream
but they're in the same research methods
folder
okay yeah and and any other things so
maybe one we can try one suggestion that
somebody has like one in analysis or a
new domain or a new entity or like let's
just do one random
thing
[Music]
um you can support the project and
earmark donations at donate. active
inference
Institute future
streams oh this will be there's actually
a few a few other interesting topics
while people are thinking about um what
else to say
okay uh P3 there are some pretty
extensive p3f methods in the repo it'll
be a later ACM uh ant stream but check
it out if you look at the
repo uh it would be awesome to have if
if someone sees like an adjacency or if
they see something that they can add to
like section
n any of these kinds of of like
Frameworks that could be awesome and
then we go oh make a kofka database that
sends messages to the Koda API to write
these grants and then post it through
mbridge to
Discord then developing the active
inference uh kernel of the infer ant
repo so python pmdp Etc Julia RX infer
other languages there's several other
languages section I okay here was just
one sort of thought on the multiply
scale science so this is just using just
a sort of standard academic ontology
here PhD student is like one
dissertation contains multiple papers
which was how it was uh concisely
described to me then a principal
investigator has a lab with multiple
dissertations overlapping
serly organizational scale is to have
multiple Labs with within one
organization and then above the
organizational scale especially in an
online context it it is a spaceship
earth situation and that's part of this
um Grand science spaceship earth
Journey
um one tiny step for an epistemic
forager one giant leap for antk
kindes flower poem okay this is going to
be a short Tennyson poem
so the the kind of background on This
was um Buckminster Fuller was on the
editor team for This Journal called
tsquare later known as shelter and Frank
lyd Wright wrote this article about how
all may may plant flowers and then I
looked that up as a title and found that
it came from this uh poem so and then
also it's going to be awesome to see how
the the cursor can enrich this too okay
the flower by Alfred
hennyson once in a golden hour I cast to
Earth a seed up there came a flower the
people said a weed to and fro they went
through my garden bow and muttering
discontent cursed me and my flower then
it grew so tall it wore a crown of light
but thieves from over the wall stole the
seed By Night SED it far and wide by
every town and Tower till all the people
cried Splendid is the flower read my
little Fable he that runs May read most
can raise the flowers now for all have
got the seed and some are pretty enough
and some are poor indeed and now again
the people call it but a weed and then I
I did this one time but I'll I'll see
where it goes this
time
explain this in the just discuss this in
the context of Open Source
it it it said some really funny
things but then that the way that kind
of connected to the doing and the like
learning and the the foraging and then
also the planting planting experiments
collaborations really proceeding on
grants um like not just planting the
seed but there's the foraging and and
like attending and being attended to and
planting and Andor
foraging for for having
Andor being able to have the seed
however that doesn't mean every foraging
trip
Etc
okay so open source you know from from
back in the
day the seed is
dismissed resistance from proprietary
software success the the theft of the
seat at night might symbolize how
proprietary companies sometimes adopt
open source principles or code without
fully embracing the open
ethos people use
it anyone can use
it the final Stan reflects the reality
of the open source ecosystem not all
projects or Forks are of equal
quality what was once novel may become
common place or even dismissed
again
wow okay thank you all the the Chatters
let's let's look at let's do one of the
let's do one more kind of permutation
let's do the explain like I am
X so we just saw the
uh outline General erator let's go to
one that has a fixed prompt it'll be
simpler take the copy rename
it
explainer control shift L go on to the
right side it could be done in line too
but but just sometimes it's more
deliberative on the right
side adopt this script to be and explain
like I am
blank analogous to the list
of Target like
languages make it
EG Target
audiences Michael wrote Angus Deon Nobel
for econometrics rec warned recently
about hidden power dynamics behind
Quantified
models helping with the interhuman
around the tech EG uncovering hidden
power or fussing forward through
competing interests is key thank you
Michael oh yeah if anyone has uh
something for in the uh 10 to 30 minutes
total let's see how far this explainer
goes and then uh anything else or like
comments or or questions that people
want
there okay
so it changed Target languages to Target
audiences keep the API key here's
translate dissertation here's explain
dissertation so replace Target languages
with target audience renamed translate
to explain updated the prompt
updated file naming adjusted log message
and print statements it's like
what you did
what accept
it okay let's tune the
uh well first let's just see if there
any other visual that that script
halted Shannon diversity indices so this
the font of course can be fixed but this
is kind of interesting this this this
may just be a a random draw but still
within the documents some have a higher
and a lower Shannon diversity of of term
usage so maybe those are more
interesting or have more
combinations heat map term frequency
heat map okay yeah y AIS you know scale
could probably be improved
but there are some things
there correlation
matrices interactive nothing output it
just halted it just maybe it's too big
of a jump networks
halted
PCA
3D in and
out think outside the boat
box what
box Quantum negotiations this showed the
vector that we kind of looked at with
the um
loadings variance
accumulation no Vector just the data
like again this is just
PCA th this was taken from the grant
processing pipeline so it was you could
look at the heat maps of different
entities top
terms just across all documents word
clouds didn't output
okay let's if there's any target
audience
uh let's see if we can do just a couple
so we get a few across
each let's have Furious 5-year-old
oh auto complete curious It's just like
that with the syntax and auto
complete but I I'll edit this down to a
few but also anyone should write in the
chat and we can include a few creative
Target
audiences skeptic
well
studied and highly
motivated
skeptic college
students undecided on their
major Michael lenon writes some
additional dashboard indicators
epistemic forging adjacency oh yeah
additional audience types okay yeah I'll
wait I'll wait a few minutes okay then
what's let's just look at the prompt
that it's going to throw and while
people write that for a minute okay so
now the functions explain dissertation
so now here's the prompt template fixed
prompt your worldclass educator task
with explaining PhD dissertation 2 a
target audience
maintain accuracy while adopting the
explanation
maintain
Integrity
dignity Mutual
dignity and accuracy while adopting the
explanation to the
audience's type of
understanding
and broader person
this adjust language these are this is
where it gets triply interesting with
how people really think about the topics
the model training and this and how it's
processed adjust this is just we we
won't go into deep editing this but this
is just what it comes up with as the
likeliest thing that you would say to
generalize across explanations as a
concept
okay thank you Michael let let's
do curious
5-year-old okay we can go rich or we can
just go more simple and and general I
would just well this one PhD
student then college student so we have
we have
5-year-old how about high
school senior you're undecided
on whether or where to go to
college pH so we have
five
17 PhD
student
Advanced um
professional Advanced technical
professional
okay Python 3 dissertation
explainer okay bug that was the the one
shot so then here's here's it'll it
maybe we need to fix the input outputs
let's go from original oh it's not
original dissertation so that's that's
like a it's just like there it didn't
take the file structure into strong
account um but in many many cases it
does it just that's where so while it's
kind of thinking that's just because
it's saying from original because I used
the word original but then it didn't
know which one of these so let's go to
make it the shifted dissertations
improved
once
clear explaining dissertation to a
curious 5-year-old boom
cursor's gotten better and better in
every version truly and uh these are
some of the minor things that you know
whether it's whether how it's cursor
side or the llm side just the the way
that it's uh doing web search for best
practices and and able to par some of
these just Arcane
syntax it's
incredible all right they are coming out
into
explain
dissertations we'll let a few accumulate
okay the goal this script doesn't really
work or this overview now needs to ad
adopt slightly but the goal of this was
to
make like let's see also it's this is
one other thing is sometimes it helps to
manually resync the index
that's the vector embedding that cursor
is using um under the
hood so it won't be able to unindexed
code it will not be able to find so I I
I even if you do add new files it it it
here now it's synced it so
now control K let's just do I think
control shift
l update this to reflect the
folder
structure input outputs functions Etc of
everything
now hundreds of changed files
right so that it's processing on
that the the the dissertation uh
explanation
proceeds let's update this so here's
another example example little minor
limitation but it'll be
handled it just pops in and out of the
text formatting this is something it's
very challenging to resolve actually in
general is is in and out of text in text
in
text especially if it's all plain
text see like this is
Fantastical that's there's there are no
such however these
are partially
accurate there aren't the
explanations so it's like wildly ad
mixed combinations of
close technical very
subtle uh errors on through just like
totally
believable but
also and then just
like okay here's how you run the script
it's like no it's
not reject
it okay
explanations all right
5-year-old okay okay first it's starting
with all right so let's let's
do okay
the Neuroscience to we're applying
Neuroscience methods to biology for a
5-year-old so this is maybe like someone
Mike L's
lab from that original field shift paper
like Neuroscience Concepts onto
developmental biology
okay what's the big idea understanding
how nature and brains work together
what's the big
idea imagine if nature like a big park
with lots of plants and animals Works a
bit like a brain this project called the
dissertation Etc why is it important
questions we want to answer what we
found out before found out about brains
we found out about biology those are the
from the two domains same
strategy new ideas nature can change
learning from
experience neuro Concepts applied to
ecosystem but I remember the paper like
what can ecosystems learn and it's it's
always coming up and it's so it's like
stabilize the metaphor raise the water
level on the metaphors overall and the
kind of T the water table to to to be
like this for every all by all how we're
going to learn more what we'll discover
why it matters what's next let's keep
exploring even little
emojis okay now let's go to high
school it's still in the it's
uh still
okay let's let's go to
PhD Neuroscience to cooking
written more in a high school
textbook style background significance
and Novelty overarching research
questions literature review overview of
neural
networks table
one I don't know how you pronounce some
of these uh tables in conversation 58
perceptron okay historical development
the culinary
Arts current state ofth Art here's the
gaps and
opportunities pretty long this is this
is looking more like well this was oh
this was for a PhD
students so this is more like here's the
kind of brief on each of the sections of
the
dissertation Neuroscience to
cooking let's see if this one has
similar
okay this is like sharing uh your your
overall outline for like quals something
High School
senior okay so this is could be
the um same one we looked at with
cooking but now for the high school
senior yeah what if cooking was not just
an art but a science because it's
Neuroscience to cooking
background significance simpler
questions but still broadly like the uh
structure of the dissertation here's
what the chapters are about but with
just one sentence instead of like
several paragraphs
there however it's structured like a
dissertation and
then yeah okay let's do a few Mills 8102
wrote I love these wild Mash I bet
there's plenty of gold in this approach
oh so so we're now we're just pushing
like kind of trickling the next few
through but let's let's go to the
shifted once so these this is these are
you know the ones that have been
improved once in a certain way
so let's
do Blake applied to Logistics so this
one was super fun I again I just wrote
make Expressions about William Blake and
add about his mythology
by examining the par parallels within
Blake's emphasis on creativity
spirituality and social critique with
the challenges faced in modern Logistics
the research used to establish a new
paradigm termed the blakean model of
logistics that prioritizes Visionary
approaches to Supply Chain
management okay William Blake's
life how can Blake's concept of
imagination and contraries and form
Innovative practices in logistics and
then if someone's like well what about
this other important concept it's like
first off it maybe it would have
selected from it second off add that to
the original synthetic domain and then
that topic will come up in approaches in
what ways can a spiritual approach to
work enhance ethical considerations in
Supply Chain management what Frameworks
can be developed to balance efficiency
and sustainability in logistics Blake's
accurate birth and death because it was
included in the factual claims
the blakean model of logistics Duality
framework balancing competing priorities
in Supply Chain
management methodology
statistic M usually a kind of mixed
method like through structured prompt or
any of these way more advanced methods
access to the literature Etc you could
have it be proposing specific hypotheses
it could even be writing the code for
for the pre-registration and everything
sustainability okay the Blake ones are
fun
um uh let's quickly look at the
prediction matter expertise domain just
just because it's it's the it's the
outlier domain so this is part of a long
running uh Dean tickle ISM with the
subject matter expertise like the
domains and then prediction matter
expertise as this kind of like
orthagonal Dimension so for this one I
did copy in a few of our specific uh
papers like about aliceon Bob way
finding so there was a few and then I
just said just expand on this concept of
of prediction matter expertise come up
with modotto come up with memes
Switching gears like a pme pro when in
doubt synthesize it
out predicting the future one cross
disciplinary inset at a time so
questions examples but it it and then so
it just invents all these examples so
that one is sort of
like that's what's that's the the
Paradox with the um pme as anme but
let's see what one of those might look
like okay so this is Health Care
principles applied to
pme so pme is what needs to be
transformed by establishing a robust
framework for user experience quality
metrics and Tech driven Solutions
Solutions Predictive Analytics patient
Centric how can we map Health Care
situations to to prediction
matters health care what how about
something with
uh with the spatial
web cognitive security to the spatial
web cooking to the spatial web
examining how principles from The
Culinary domain can enhance user
experience design in digital
environments how can what works for
restaurants as as places and times and
experiences work
for spatial
web how
about prediction matter expertise to
spatial web
and then again when it's like oh I would
have said something different first off
we can have many branches of people's
models but also then just we edit the
source
document this seems to highlight just a
predictive
statistics and adaptability
angle but then the language analysis can
be like on these and then you can do it
on the explanations and and one of one
of the interesting and I think helpful
ways to think about a few of these
operations that are happening is like
the principal component analysis on the
term frequency uses so let me pull that
one up and
then so here turn frequencies are being
used across within an across documents
so in this situation if you had uh
X dissertations in the folder and then
you're going to translate into a bunch
of different languages like l so if you
cluster on syntax like term usage then
the languages are going to Cluster
together because they're using terms
that are like exclusive to one language
or another character sets even if you
clustered on
semantics then the dissertation would
cluster together across languages which
convey in in the case of an accurate
translation like
similarish semantics so that's basically
the difference between syntax and
semantics and that's something that's
really opened up with these methods is
what what I've been showing with the
term frequency type analyses syntax
based methods they're still very cool
and there's actually a lot of
information in them however what cursor
especially but the language models
overall are enabling is just
like arbitrary
semantic
discussion
so thank you Michael you know explain
the
at field shift overall to a
clam okay Advanced technical here we
[Music]
go Neuroscience to
blockchain for advanced technical
professional
foundational work proposed integrative M
model neurochain adaptive consensus
learning smart
contracts mix method case studies
surveys interviews simulations
analytical
approaches so here's
that's the explanation script is running
oh here's the
clam you're nestled in your cozy ocean
bed and suddenly the water around you
starts to change that's a a bit like
what field shift does but for
researchers studying the world above the
waves field shift is a special tool that
helps scientists understand how the
environment is changing
interesting field shift collects a lot
of data about the environment like
temperature rainfall and plant growth
it's
like what so that's kind of the funny
again the the the
huge the huge range of what comes out in
different
contexts let's look at a few more random
dissertations yeah these are the ones
that were made more recently but we
halted that
one let's just look at one or two more
okay William Blake oh we we looked at a
Blake one already but we haven't looked
at a let's look at one Fe see this whole
Fe applied to
X this is
like I hope broadening the scope it's
like it's not just a to B for FP to that
the the the the immediately available
adjacency space is domains to the second
power for starter even before imposing
other more High dimensional aspects for
interdisciplinary from to two but then
there's other structures of synthesis
other kinds of patterns that that can be
emulated but this is just the from to
two
um so we have whatever expressions and
claims we put in about FP and actm that
fit in with uh the the llm schema SL
length and and attributes th this is the
starting point or a starting point for
some of those discussions so
here's Fe mitob
biology transposing the free energy
principle to mitochondrial
function how can predictive coding and
active inference be applied to
mitochondrial function
different methods like that would relate
to the to the actual working it
out FP to an ATM
transaction it transcends the immediate
context of self-service banking it holds
broader implications for adaptive
systems in technology and user
experience design
first principles for the
ATM FP to Quantum something that that is
happening so in the context Andor in the
files or it it
may F
priston how can the concept of PF be
applied to optimize Quantum algorithms
in what ways do generative models and Fe
correspond to Quantum States and Quantum
computation what are the implications of
active inference for the measurement
processes in Quantum
systems
okay FP to cooking
how does predictive coding and active
inference apply to flavor development in
culinary practices and what ways can
generative models inform the evolution
of Cuisines and culinary Fusion what
educational Frameworks can be developed
to integrate FP Concepts into culinary
training so um the last edit I want to
make is just to update the readme and
then push that so that
it is accurate for when and then I can
update the um description in the code or
in the uh
YouTube for where all the folders
are if anyone has a last comment though
please feel free to ask a comment or
question
position 10 slow
request so even when I'm way over 500 oh
also here's here's what's what else is
amazing going to reload the
page I don't think anything will sh
I've spent $112 on this whole whole
phase of the project first API call I
made was on August 1st to gbt 40 I was
like okay that's the best model right
wrote two of like the two of the first
step two first two shifted domains
stopped it wait five minutes reload was
like oh no well that was that was $3 oh
$150 it's like okay and then I I looked
up I asked perplexity I was like what
are the costs and everything and what's
the best one for for for large shock
it's like oh GPT 40 it's like okay so
that's $2 today and then yesterday when
when I went through all the uh I mean
when it was going through all the uh
like 484 whatever it was that was
$3
then
activity number of
tokens so now now it's hidden to fast
but that's even just with a couple
python ter
here's gbd4
mini that was 11 million 11.7 million
tokens for
$3 so token's not exactly a word but
like this is on the order depending on
on everything etc etc I don't know but
it's it's it's not it's not 10 10x and
it's not a tenth so it's an incredible
amount of text processing
today 6.8 million
tokens for
$241
$242 and then
cursor so cursor I'm paying $20 a month
this is just to describe the method
methodological and the the kind of
financial not the time side but just
like cursor $20 a month for the 500 Fast
requests but then the slow ones are not
that bad so I don't I don't know how it
is not with at at all but but it's it's
clearly worth um that and and Beyond
then the API calls for open AI oh uh
some colleagues shared the open router I
think it's a great idea to like improve
the llm handling make that more flexible
be able to do that locally Etc um but
just to use what was working now
for several dollarss to to create um
these all by alls do the shift make the
outline write the draft improve the
draft translate to
arbitrary contrl K add
the dis add
the explainer
into the visualization all right any
last comments then I'll end it and push
it after this
it's like it just says
no maybe if I don't call it
explanation
still okay curious
5-year-old let's see little
Blake Neuroscience blockchain
chemistry okay Neuroscience to
Blake this special study looks at a
famous artist and poet named William
Blake and how his IDE are like the way
our brains talk to each other how can we
think about Blake's ideas like a
brain what can we learn from mixing
brain science and
stories here again
no well I guess it isn't to be right
now check for any last read
me but and and the folder structure May
slightly change uh these are all just
early working folders I think fonds
underneath research underneath methods
underneath one this might be a good
source for for for longer reference to
uh like grants and and to structure that
better but already in the research
methods folder this is where all the
grant methods
are but that's kind of Grant meth
methods 1.0 so we can make it kind of
Grant methods 2.0 field shift Plus+ plus
field shift 3 and that would uh maybe
with more flexibility like select the
promp select the entity combination
maybe select the order and then we could
just we could get rolling on on many
fronts whereas actually like you know in
its own meta way this was manual with
heavy augmentation for a lot of all by
all considered as text files but
but but structurally manually DED so it
could be distilled and
improved
okay I'll just wait one more minute to
read anything people WR while
I end the stream push to get
help it's it's going to be a active
project at The Institute for the active
infant project so people can contribute
acing synchronously with questions
issues documentation on the coda pages
in The
GitHub uh if someone wants to work on
this or integrate it with some other way
please just contact me we can figure out
the right Institute related or or just
other Arrangement and add a bunch of
pieces to all of this and just part of
the beauty of the the code and the open
source system is like it it hopefully
can ratchet the function like this
doesn't do it all but now this is a
starting point and the outputs even if
you don't run any code at all in the
GitHub you can still see the outputs so
I'll push it we'll look at the
GitHub final
and push
prepare
methods research field shift to
everything's in here inputs
outputs shift to
dissertations
crlf you know
just whatever you want to search for
Lake it'll search on both
sides Blake to
Neuroscience here it
is translated
dissertations Sanskrit
here it
is I don't
know cool all
right thank you upcycle thank you Mills
818 thank you
8102 thank you Andrew yeah all right
well uh we're
live the calls go on so I I hope uh
people who are interested share it and
the the repo and the video and let's do
infra ant streams to develop so many of
these fractal functionalities of this
repo that has long been in the
institute's
domain Andrew wrote wondering if a
separate 10ish minute setup tutorial on
how to reproduce the cursor python
GitHub integration would be helpful for
others to
contribute yeah yeah great suggestion
like make the issue on the GitHub and
then I'll make it an issue and then
we'll get it to it cool all right thank
you
bye for